smashingbuzz.com 2017-12-01

# Privacy Policy

smashingbuzz.com has a determination to protect your policy. This privacy policy lets you know as why we collect online data, what are its purposes and where it is used? The terms of our policy are so simple, no different terms and conditions are applied!

If you are a regular user of the website you will be agree with the terms of this policy. smashingbuzz has particular operating set-up and this is simple and easy to access. We control users’ entire data and process it too. The collected data might be retained, accessed, processed, may be stored and deployed in jurisdictions whose privacy rules are a bit different and bottommost protective as compare to your home jurisdiction. smashingbuzz team is conscious to give users’ complete protection from all edges.

### Cookies And Web Beacons

smashingbuzz.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on smashingbuzz.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to smashingbuzz.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the

following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include: [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/adsense)  and [Amazon](https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/).

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on smashingbuzz.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

smashingbuzz.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You can however opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of our sites and services that depend on cookies. In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies to collect personal information and help personalize your online experience.

### Collection of Your Personal Information

We need your information at different steps! When you visit our site some specific sections of information are required like the referred site, your IP address, language, operating time and browser type might be collected automatically as a part of the site operation. The assigned team also collects the navigational information such as information about the pages you see, any other actions required in links and the links you click on the site. Also we collect your demographically info that includes your interests, hobbies, gender, income and age. You provide an email address to complete the commenting process for email communications.

### Where we Use Your Personal Information?

You don’t worry about your info because it is secure with us we use it just for formalities. We use your personal details for the site, to maintain your transactions, to give customer services in a better way, to accomplish research and analysis targeted at improving our products, tech and services. We present content that meet your needs.

Also we get your details just to contact with you as sends you the marketing communication materials, sends email, newsletter and the latest promotions. We keep your record in specific areas where it is absolutely safe. We don’t use it for illegal purpose but just use it to fulfill the blank and required area.

### Where We Share Your Collected Information?

Except as it has been revealed in this Privacy policy, smashingbuzz team doesn’t share your info with anyone.  Our team compiles up users’ particular piece of information that includes volunteered information from readers and pages consumers visit or access like as a look off of website registration. The collected info is helpful to improve the content of the website just in a technical fashion. Perhaps we share your details with our corporate group like divisions, subsidiaries affiliated companies, and they all use your personal info to fulfill the required purposes. In some cases we share your info with 3rd party service providers who work on our behalf. Our company reserves the right to show off your piece of info if need to do so by law either in the excellent dogma that such working is reasonably compulsory to cover up with legal procedure, replies to claims or secures the rights, property of the company,  public, customers and employees.

### Use of Cookies and Other Technologies

Our company uses cookies to preserve visitor preferences, maintain user-particular information on what page users approach, balances the website content contains on visitors browser type or other details that visitors sends. In some situations our 3rd party service provider might use cookies on the sites. Our team has no control over the cookies. We cover the use of cookies by smashingbuzz not the use of cookies by third parties. You have the competency to reject and accept cookies. Several browsers accept cookies but you can change your browser settings to retain cookies. If you select to retain cookies you might not be able to login or deploy other amazing features of our site and services that concern on cookies.

### Advertising

We support you to introduce your identity in the market! You can advertise with ease by using different banners, links, distributions, downloads and other details accessed directly or either indirectly from the host promotion within its website and holds the right to make changes and manage content without notification. Our team is not responsible for the 3rd party banners as in any situation if any omissions or errors are made by them that is not set in this privacy policy.

### Information Security

smashingbuzz has specific security measures in place in our tangible facilities and the facilities of our service providers to secure against the damage, change or misuse of info that our team has collected for users’ on our website.  The collected detail of the visitors is kept confidential and this is used for technical and editorial improvements to the website.

### Copyright

The blog posts you write for us must not be copied, translated, reproduced, communicated, distributed or displayed in any way without already written consent of smashingbuzz.

### Content

The suggestions, views and opinions showed in the media, articles or comments on this site are linked to those speakers and doesn’t show off the comments about our site.

Rather we assure you that the provided details are non-misleading and rectify the best of our knowledge. We do not warrant the regulations, integrity, fulfillness or timeless of the information consists of our site. However if you have any complaint then feel free to contact us and give us your suggestions.

### Modifications to This Privacy Policy

smashingbuzz has the authority to alter the terms of this privacy policy as well as disclaimer at any moment without any proper notification. When our team does changes we shall revise that recent update, provide the date on the top of the policy.

### Contact Information

Please feel free to contact smashingbuzz by completing just a few steps on the contact page or you can email us for your concern questions.
